And I started from like the ground up where I knew nothing and
I was building something to where I feel like...
Like you literally built the machine.
And so I had to understand.
I think like people coming into the lab in a semester when things
have been built, and they're just kind of like,
I never got the chance to learn any of this.
And then the feedback cycle can become, that didn't work, try
again.
Yeah.
That didn't work, try again.
AI could write the first draft of a paper that then we read
and really understand
Xavier was explaining the Bayesian optimization to Seth and
I was listening in and I could tell that Xavier really understood
that he wasn't just using AI to do the learning